A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of Experimental Medicine, Accepted Manuscripts, Series 1 FA972
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of Experimental Medicine, Accepted Manuscripts, Series 1
1972-1983
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller University Press
FA972
1.69 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, 1 letter document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 517-2-U
Other Finding Aids
FA971 Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of Experimental Medicine, Microfiche.
Arrangement
Alphabetical.
Scope and Contents
Consists of correspondence and notes related to the submission, evaluation, and acceptance of manuscripts for publication in the Journal of Experimental Medicine.
- Correspondence - A, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- Correspondence - B, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- Correspondence - C, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
- Correspondence - D, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
- Correspondence - F, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
- Correspondence - G, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
- Correspondence - P, 1972-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20-23)
- Correspondence - S, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
- Correspondence - T, 1972-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
- Correspondence - W, 1972-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4-7)